waggers
字幕组
- 嗨 - 嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
噢 好吃的
Oh, yum.
- 给我来点 - 不 Grace 别
- Give me some. - No, Grace, don't.
噢 天啊 太恶心了
Oh God. That's disgusting.
- 这是什么? - 水果奶昔
- What is that? - Fruit shake.
什么水果会是灰色的?
What fruit is gray?
梨
Pears.
什么?
What?
- 噢 - 噢 这是…
- Oh. - Oh, for--
噢 蛋白粉?
Oh, Mondo Fuel?
你想变得壮起来
You're trying to bulk up.
不 这只是膳食补充剂
No, it's a dietary supplement.
不 才不是
No, it's not.
你想要粗壮的臂膀
You want za big arms.
好让你勾搭阳刚的男人
So you can get za big men,
然后引诱他们到你的小窝里干柴烈火
and lure them into your den of zoom-zoom.
好的 非常感谢你的解说
Okay, thank you very much.
够了 Grace
That'll be enough, Grace.
- 噢 天啊 发生了什么? - 什么?
- Oh my God, what's happening? - What?
你的扣子都崩开了 衬衫也撕裂了
Your buttons are popping. Your shirt is ripping.
你要变成无敌浩克了! 你都变绿了!
You're hulking up! You're turning green!
谢谢你啊 顺带一提 这玩意儿碰巧也对你有好处的
Thank you. Excuse me, this happens to be good for you.
噢 天啊
Oh my God.
这上面说还能丰胸
It says it also grows breast tissue.
你想试试吗?
You want to give it a try?
你知道 我以为我了解你的一切
You know I thought I knew everything about you,
引用英国首相丘吉尔名言 "It is a riddle, wrapped in a mystery, inside an enigma."
但你其实是镜中花 水中月
but you're a mystery, wrapped in a riddle,
全身围绕着英格玛密码 还不断地在长胸
surrounded by enigma, growing boobies.
二战中德国使用的加密编码机
话说回来 你怎么样?
Anyway, how are you?
还不错 Karen 要去度假了
I'm okay. Karen's going on vacation,
所以这周我要找个助理
so I need to find an assistant for the week.
Karen 整天做的就是锉指甲 翻购物册
Karen files her nails, and thumbs through catalogues all day.
她度假时都做什么?
What's she gonna do on a vacation?
我猜她会办公吧
I guess office work.
噢 天哪
Oh my God.
听着 免开尊口 站着说话不腰疼
Look, don't. It's too easy.
随便给我一件衣服穿
Just give me something' to wear,
因为我不想穿着这身
'cause I can't walk another block
克林贡戏服再走一步路了
in this Klingon suit.
《星际迷航》(Star Trek) 中的外星种族 生性好战
你打扮成这样 还指望我们不嘲笑你
You want us to not make fun of you looking like that.
那真是... 不合逻辑
That would be... illogical.
《星际迷航》中 Spock 的常用词
坐下来 外星服务员 跟我们倒倒苦水
Sit, alien cater-waiter. Tell us of your pain.
都怪 Brandon Schwartz 的星舰主题成人礼
Brandon Schwartz's Star Fleet bar mitzvah.
现场布置: 企业号航空母舰
The decor, USS Enterprise.
《星际迷航》中舰艇名
菜单: 跨星系犹太洁食
The menu, intergalactic kosher.
更别提
Not to mention,
有个小博格人吐了我一身
one of the little Borgs barfed all over my clothes.
《星际迷航》中的高科技种族 半人半机械
舰长 经过近距离勘察
Captain, after closer examination,
我相信 我已经鉴定出了新物种
I believe I have identified the life form as
"弯星人"
"Gaylien."
我们爱好和平 请不要重新布置我们的家具
We come in peace. Please do not rearrange our furniture.
好玩吧? 拜拜了
You know what? Goodbye.
好 好 我们不玩了
Okay, okay. We'll stop.
不 你才不会呢 因为你就是无法自制
No, you won't, because you can't help yourself.
你天生毒舌 卑鄙无耻
You were born bitter, nasty,
居心险恶 当然了 还有膀大腰圆
mean- spirited and, of course, chunky.
另外 Grace 你也没好到哪里去
And, Grace, you're not much better.
你就是个没有半分体面的小跟班
You are a follower without an ounce of decency.
Jack 你想到我办公室上一星期班吗?
Jack, do you want to work in my office for a week?
不过你倒是有改变自己的能力
Although you have the ability to change,
这就是我一直很喜欢你的地方
and that's what I've always liked about you.
Karen 去度假了
Karen's going on vacation.
我需要有人帮我接接电话
I need someone to help with the phones.
-工作时间? - 很短
- Hours? - Minimal.
- 有牙医津贴? - 包午饭
- Dental? - Lunch.
-我觉得我们可以谈拢 - 很好
- I think we can work something out. - Great.
噢 你们姐妹俩肯定玩得不亦乐乎
Oh, you girls are gonna have a ball,
相互编辫子 谈谈男孩子
braidin' each other's hair, and talkin' about boys,
做一做《时尚 COSMO》上的小测验
and doin' the Cosmo quiz.
比方说 "如何鉴定你的好朋友是不是贱人?"
You mean like, "How To Tell lf Your Best Friend's A Bitch?"
鉴定完毕 你是
Yeah, already took it. You are.
本字幕由waggers字幕组与zimuzu联合制作
翻译 黎巴  时间轴 残狱
William Tell 瑞士民间传说中的英雄
第一季 第六集 威尔的秘密
S01E06 William Tell
校对 Buble Water
特效 Buble  压制 Water
Karen Walker 想要见你
Karen Walker's here to see you.
开玩笑吧
You're kidding.
让她进来
Send her in.
他当然是啦
Of course he is.
比彩虹还要弯 亲爱的
As a $3 bill, honey.
出自短语 "Queer as a three dollar bill" 就像三美元假币一样假
Queer 双关假币/同志
她是刚从船上摔下来还是怎么了?
Did she just fall off the boat or what?
Off the boat 暗指不了解风俗的移民 调侃看不出 Will 是同志
除了在办公室前台帮我出柜之外 有何贵干?
What are you doing here besides outing me to the front office?
好吧 首先… 噢 Will
Well, first of-- oh, Will.
绿色调
The green,
不行
no.
这些法律书籍倒还蛮可爱的
The lawbooks are kind of cute, though.
然后你竟然在地下室工作?
And you work in a basement?
亲爱的 你得搬到楼上去
Honey, you've gotta move up from the street.
要不然 你就得整天坐在这儿
Otherwise, you're sittin' around all day
让廉价鞋子践踏你的眼睛
watchin' bad shoes go by.
看吧 玖熙
See, Nine West.
我喜欢这个办公室
I love this office.
看看这些雕花 这个地方历史厚重
Look at these moldings. This place has historical significance.
他们拍摄《冲突》的地方就在…
They filmed "Serpico" Just a--
西德尼·吕美特执导的1973年奥斯卡提名电影
为什么我要替一栋楼辩护?
why am I defending my building?
Karen 你想要什么?
Karen, what do you want?
嗯 我想要的是…
Well, what I want--
给你弄条新地毯
is for you to get a new rug.
噢 亲爱的
Oh, honey.
这儿太杂乱了 品味太差
It's too busy, it's shoddy,
我正在考虑离婚
I'm thinking of leaving my husband,
- 还有这些窗户的布置! - 什么? 什么?
- and those window treatments! - What? What?
竹子? 这是家律师事务所 又不是迪斯尼提基神殿
Bamboo? This is a law firm, not The Tiki-Tiki Room.
Enchanted Tiki Room 迪斯尼乐园游乐设施 树屋景观
- Karen! - 你怎么能…
- Karen! - How can you--
别管窗帘了 说说你丈夫
Forget the blinds. Your husband?
你和 Stan 怎么了?
What's happening with you and Stan?
我们本来准备登机 开启黑珍珠扫货之旅
We were about to get on our plane to go black pearl shopping
前往波拉波拉岛
in Bora Bora,
突然之间 我看着 Stan
when all of a sudden, I looked at Stan,
恍然大悟
and it dawned on me,
婚姻不应该如此劳碌的
marriage shouldn't be this much work.
Karen 我是个公司委托律师
Karen, I'm a corporate attorney.
你需要的是一位出色的离婚律师
What you need is a good divorce lawyer
或者只是一位出色的药剂师
or perhaps just a good pharmacist.
你们这种人毒舌起来都不打结的
The nastiness comes so easily to your people.
拜托 Will 不要装得屈尊降贵
Come on, Will. Don't patronize me.
我非常清楚你是哪种律师
I know exactly what kind of lawyer you are,
没名气的那种
an obscure one.
所以我才需要你
And that's why I need you.
我得弄清楚 Stan 的公司财产
I have to find out about Stan's corporate holdings
- 还不能让他发现 - 真的吗?
- without him knowing. - Really?
真有王雪琴的风范
This is so Alexis Carrington.
八十年代美剧《豪门恩怨》(Dallas) 中人物 石油大亨前妻
别闹 听着 我是认真的
Come on. Look, I'm serious.
我开始觉得 我好像已经不再拥有我的丈夫了
I'm starting to feel as if I don't own my own husband anymore.
你是说 你已经不再了解你的丈夫了
You mean you don't know your own husband anymore.
- 我刚才就是这么说的啊 亲爱的 - 不 你…
- That's what I just said, honey. - No, you--
你说的是"拥有"
you said "Own."
不 我说的是 我感觉我不再拥有我自己的… 好像我…
No, I said I feel like I don't own my own-- Like I don't--
哎呀 好了 叮铃铃
Oh, all right! Ding! Ding! Ding!
你会一站到底的 机灵鬼!
You'd win on Jeopardy, smart guy!
《危险边缘》(Jeopardy) 益智问答游戏节目
当事人保密特权什么时候才生效?
When does the attorney's client privilege kick in?
收到支票 即时生效
As soon as the client gives the attorney a check,
但… 不 Karen
but-- no, Karen.
让我当你的律师…
Me as your lawyer--
让我当你的律师 就这么定了
me as your lawyer, consider it done.
我告诉你一些你可能不知道的 Will 逸事
Here's something you probably don't know about Will.
上小学的时候 Will 暗地里超喜欢一本书…
In elementary school, Will secretly loved the book--
《上帝 您在吗? 是我 玛格丽特》
"Are You There, God? It's Me, Margaret".
大学时这本书让我们心手相牵
We bonded over it in college.
- 那好 你知不知道Will… - 噢 拜托
- Okay, did you know that Will-- - Oh, please.
等到你比我更了解 Will 的那天
The day you know more about Will than I do,
我会很乐意亲你屁股
is the day I gladly kiss your butt.
帮帮忙 把流苏分好类
Do me a favor. Sort these tassels.
你想要按颜色分 还是按尺寸分?
You want me to sort them by color or by size?
按5点之前分好的标准分
By 5:00.
你想表现表现吗? 去帮帮你身后那个人
You want to be useful? Help the man standing behind you
他的包裹很大
with the big package.
Package 双关 包裹/鼓裆内的活儿
Grace 别调戏我
Grace, don't tease me.
- 你好 - 是 Grace Adler 设计室吗?
- Hello. - Grace Adler Design?
我来签收吧
I'll sign for it.
签名字就行了 先生 我不需要你的号码
Just your name, sir. I don't need your phone number.
别这么确定
Don't be so sure.
先生
sir.
Jack?
Jack? Jack!
嗨 你能帮我把它放在后面吗?
Hi. Can you put that in the back, please?
谢谢你
Thank you.
哇噢 要我说 那家伙和 Steven 长得一模一样
Wow, tell me that guy did not look exactly like Steven.
- 哪个 Steven? - Will 的 Steven
- Who's Steven? - Will's Steven.
- Will 没有什么 Steven - 好吧 不再有了
- Will doesn't have a Steven. - Well, not anymore,
你懂的...
but you know--
噢
Oh.
你不知道谁是 Steven
You don't know who Steven is.
唔 手滑
Oops, butterfingers.
我猜呀 空头支票还是不要乱开
I guess one shouldn't make any promises they can't keep.
心中有爱 面带微笑 来吧
With love in your heart, and a smile on your face.
快告诉我 Steven 是谁就行了
Just tell me who Steven is.
我正翘臀以待呢
I'm waiting.
- 每小时加两块 - 听我道来
- Two bucks more an hour. - I'm talking.
Steven 是他以前事务所的同事
Steven was a guy at his old law firm.
他们有过那么一小段
They had a little fling
去年夏天的事 那时他还和 Michael 在一起
last summer while he was still seeing Michael.
让我用四个字形容 鲜嫩多汁
And let me just say, Hotty McHot.
咝
Ss-sss.
- 去年夏天? - 是的
- Last summer? - Yeah.
他那时称他是"客户" 这是他的暗号
He used to call him a client. That was his code word.
"我要和一个客户吃晚饭"
"I'm having dinner with a client.
"我要给一个客户起草陈述"
I'm drawing up some briefs for a client."
的确是和"陈述"有关
There were some briefs involved,
Brief 双关 案件陈述/短裤
只不过他并没做"起草"那部分
but he wasn't drawin' them up.
- 嘿 - 嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
准备好听听我计划的二人之夜了吗?
Ready to hear what I have planned for us tonight?
首先 我要无视我所有的饮食问题
First of all, I'm putting aside all of my food issues.
准备好 今晚 我们吃小麦
So get ready, tonight, we eat wheat.
圣经中用 wheat 比喻纯朴诚实的信徒
那么
So
和 Jack 一起工作
Workin' with Jack.
他等了多长时间
How long did it take
才忍不住扯了一匹你的丝绸帷幔
before he took one of your silk drapery panels,
围在身上当纱笼穿的?
and wore it like a sarong?
印尼及马来西亚地区民族服装
你干嘛用这种眼神看我?
Why are you looking at me like that?
《我知道你去年夏天干了什么》
"I Know What You Did Last Summer."
1997年惊悚片
什么?
Pardon?
那部电影 我租的
The movie. I rented it.
-《我知道你去年夏天干了什么》 - "去年夏天" 噢 我懂了
- "I Know What You Did Last Summer." - "Last Summer," Oh, I see.
和这部《风流韵事》
And "An Affair To Remember."
1957年爱情片
以及这部《客户》
With "The Client."
1994年警匪片
- 你觉得怎么样? - 我觉得好电影都被别人借了
- What do you think? - All the good movies were taken.
我还觉得今晚你得一个人看这些电影了
I think you're also gonna have to watch them alone.
- 为什么 你要去哪? - 我要去见一个客户
- Why, where you going? - I gotta meet with a client.
一个什么?
A what?
一个客户
A client.
- 晚上九点? - 是啊
-At 9:00 at night? - Yeah.
只有这时候我们俩才都有空
It's the only time we could both do it.
- 是谁? - 就是个客户而已
- Who is it? - It's just a client.
一个新客户 明天早上再见
It's a new client. I'll see you in the morning.
噢 小麦别吃太多 行吗?
Oh, and go easy on the wheat, huh?
我不想回到家 发现你躺在地上
I don't want to come home, and find you lying on the floor
攥着手机 手指才摁到9
clutching the phone with your finger on the nine.
麸质过敏症 与 小麦过敏
美国急救电话911
Jack 太好了 你还在
Jack, good, you're still there.
是啊
Yeah.
我还在等那个大包裹
I'm still waiting for that package.
Grace 你这些丝绸帷幔在哪搞到的?
Grace, where did you get these drapery panels?
- 翡翠纺织 怎么了? - 没事
- Emerald Fabric, why? - No reason.
你问到 Steven 的时候 Will 什么反应?
What did Will say when you asked him about Steven?
我一直没机会问他那个客户的事 为什么?
I never got to ask him about that client. Why?
- 因为他有了个新客户 - 你说什么?
- Because he has a new client. - What are you talking about?
噢 别跟我装傻 他在约会 Jack
Oh, like you don't know. He's seeing someone, Jack.
我不敢相信你又瞒着我
I can't believe you kept this from me.
我什么都不知道
I didn't know anything about it.
不 肯定是别的什么
No, it's gotta be something else.
再说 他交桃花运的几率太小了
Besides, the odds are against him.
过去八年 他只和五个人在一起过
He's only been with five people in the last eight years.
他就像一只没人爱的座头鲸
He's like a humpback whale.
没人"做"的座头鲸
Without the hump.
噢 天哪 那究竟是发生了什么?
Oh my God. So what could it be?
会是什么事 他既不告诉你 也不告诉我?
What could it be that he didn't tell you, and he didn't tell me?
肯定是他不想让我们知道的事
It must be something he didn't want us to know.
干得漂亮 少女妙探 我们待会在老神秘河上汇合
Good work, Nancy Drew. Let's meet up at Old Mystery Creek.
悬疑小说人物 最早出现于1930年 后出版多部小说和相关影视剧
Jack 赶紧过来
Jack, just get over here now.
还有放下帷幔
And lose the drapes.
我在电话里都听见它们摩擦的声音
I can hear the fabrics rustling through the phone.
我能不能…
Can I--
我们能作为朋友聊一会吗?
Can I talk to you for a minute as if we were friends?
噢 亲爱的
Oh, honey.
我知道 我知道 我没有给你好脸色看
I know, I know, I give you a hard time,
我还嘲笑你从来不干任何工作
and I make jokes about how you never do any work.
很好笑 因为这是实话
But it's funny because it's true.
我知道
I know.
如果你决定要离婚 我可以帮你
If you're set on divorce, I can help you with that,
但是感情上需要承担很多
but it's gonna take an emotional toll.
噢 我不知道 Will
Oh, I don't know, Will.
从许多层面讲 我都过得很好
In a lot of ways, I have a very good life.
城里一套房 郊区一套房 轮船
A home in the city, a home in the country, a boat,
珠宝 艺术品 豪车 一个厨子 一个教练
jewelry, art, cars, a chef, a trainer,
- 一个碉堡的衣橱… - 是是 我知道
- an ass-kicking wardrobe-- - Yeah, I get it.
那这个碉堡衣橱里的女人 是怎么样的呢?
How is the woman inside the ass-kicking wardrobe?
体脂率 9% 感觉有些迷茫
9% body fat and a little bit lost.
Will 我不知道建立亲密关系需要付出什么
Will, I don't know what it takes to make a good relationship.
我也不是专家
I'm no expert,
但我生命中最重要的关系
but the key relationships in my life
就是建立在交流和信任之上的
are based on communication and trust.
他藏了些什么? 什么事会如此糟糕?
What is he hiding? What could be so bad?
为什么他不信任我?
Why doesn't he trust me?
不知道 可能是因为你正在翻他的东西吧
I don't know. Maybe it's 'cause you're rifling through his stuff.
别误会 这事我经常干
Don't get me wrong, I do this all the time.
只不过你们从来没逮着我
You're just never here when it happens.
噢 别担心 你的房间 无聊
Oh, don't worry. Your room, boring.
再跟我说一遍 我们在找什么
So, tell me again what we're looking for.
宣告噩耗的东西
Something that spells doom.
什么?
What?
他把所有的巧克力软糖都吃光了
He ate all the Mallomars.
天哪 他在压力性暴食
Oh my God. He's stress eating.
他暴饮暴食是因为… 他的事业面临困境
He's eating because-- his business is folding.
- 你觉得他的事业面临困境了? - 全都解释得通了
- You think his business is folding? - It all makes sense.
他的确是问过我 什么时候才能还欠他的25,000美元
He actually asked me when I would pay back the 25,000.
不... 这种事他会告诉我的 肯定是更严重的事
No... That, he would tell me. It has to be something worse.
天啊 他到底瞒着我什么?
God, what is he keeping from me?
噢 天哪 是毒品
Oh my God. It's drugs.
是毒品 他在吸毒
It's drugs. He's doing drugs.
居然不带我
Without me.
不是说我想吸 但至少也先问问我嘛
Not that I do drugs, but I'd like to be asked.
你知道还有什么事他不会告诉我们吗? 他生病了
You know what else he wouldn't tell either of us? If he's sick.
他需要换肾 噢 天哪 他需要换肾
He needs a kidney. Oh my God, he needs a kidney.
不是说我会捐 但至少也先问问我嘛
Not that I would give him a kidney, but I'd like to be asked.
- Jack 快去检查他的卧室 - 好吧 我要找什么?
- Jack, go check his bedroom. - Okay what am I looking for?
噩耗
Doom.
从他的床开始
I'll start with his bed.
啊哈! 找到了!
A-ha! I found something!
- 什么?! - Will 的新外套
- What?! - Will's new jacket.
我穿着有点大 但爱死这面料了
I'm swimming in it, but loving the fabric.
我觉得这里什么都没有
I don't think there's anything here.
噢 难怪这儿鼓鼓囊囊的 他的日程本在口袋里
Oh, no wonder it's so bulky. His day planner's in here.
- 这是不对的 - 你觉得我们应该把它收起来?
- This is wrong. - You think we should put it away?
不 月份不对
No, it's the wrong month.
好的 在这里 他会在 Astor 咖啡厅吃晚饭
Okay, here it is. He's having dinner at the Astor Cafe...
- 和K一起 - K? 肾!
- with K. - K? Kidney!
但是他不可能和肾一起吃饭啊
But he wouldn't be having dinner with one.
Astor 咖啡厅
The Astor Cafe.
- 不 我不行 - 你可以的
- No, I can't. - You could.
- 我不会这样做 - 你会的
- I won't. - You will.
- 你说得对 - 好
- You're right. - Yes.
看起来尽管如此
It seems like despite everything,
你还是爱着你丈夫的
you're still in love with your husband.
我觉得很多层面上 我都有点像一个年轻版
I guess in a lot of ways I'm kind of like a younger,
更加美艳版的 Leona Helmsley
much more beautiful version of Leona Helmsley.
美国酒店业女富豪 以浮华生活和暴戾性格闻名 人称"苛刻女皇"
首先 你为钱结婚
First, you marry for money,
然后 你发现自己爱上了这个糟老头
and then you find yourself lovin' the old coot.
接着 他就暴毙 最后 你分到了家产
Then he drops dead, and you get the money anyway.
- 这是个双赢 - 我太感动了
- It's a win-win. - My heart is full.
手机给我 我现在就想给 Stan 打电话
Give me your phone. I wanna call Stan right this minute.
- 头 头 头 - 有什么事吗?
- Head, head, head. - Can I help you?
- 不 我只是来这里找人的 - 你需要预约
- No, I'm just here to see someone. - You need a reservation.
找人也要预约?
To see someone?
我们要保护我们的顾客
We like to protect our patrons.
你觉得我能干什么?
What do you think I'm gonna do?
在餐厅里跑来跑去 然后在他们的食物里撒盐?
Run around the dining room, and oversalt their food?
谁是我的狗狗 哈?
Who's my puppy, huh?
谁是我淘气 下流的小狗狗?
Who's my naughty, naughty little puppy?
尾巴摇起来
Wag that tail.
就这样 给我摇
That's right, wag it.
啊噢
Uh-oh.
噢 我认识一只非常 非常顽皮 又淘气的狗狗
Oh, I know a very, very bad, naughty puppy
又要戴上他的项圈了
who's gonna have to go back on his leash.
不好意思 我可以结账了吗?
Excuse me, could I get the check?
另外我需要一架离开这里的飞机
And an airlift out of here?
噢 Stan?
Oh, Stan?
待会再打给你 我又接到了一通电话
I'm gonna have to call you back. I'm gettin' another call,
回头见 嗯哼
but I'll see you later. Mm-hmm.
开始做仰卧起坐吧
Start doing your sit-ups.
给你 亲爱的 有你的电话 我得去补个妆
Here, honey, you got a call. And I have to go re-apply.
你好
Hello.
嗨 是我
Hi, it's me.
我只想知道 你有没有
I just wanted to know if there was,
就是 有没有什么事想告诉我
you know, anything that you wanted to tell me.
- 你在说什么事? - 你有事瞒着我
- What are you talking about? - You're hiding something from me.
- 是什么事? - 你吃了多少小麦?
- What is it? - How much wheat did you have?
为什么不告诉我 Steven 的事?
Why didn't you tell me about Steven?
- Steven? - 对啊! 我还是从…
- Steven? - Yes! I had to find out from--
噢! 见鬼!
oh! Damn it!
我再也不会
That's the last time
为了一双赠品连裤袜 而买一部手机了
I buy a phone to get a free pair of pantyhose.
喂?
Hello?
我们的约法三章里可没有相互隐瞒
Keeping secrets is not in our rule book.
关于 K 的事我都知道了
I know all about K.
好吧 其实 我并不是什么都知道
Well, actually, I don't know all about K.
事实上 关于 K 我什么都不知道 谁是 K?
Actually, I don't know anything about K. Who's K?
等一下 喂?
Hold on. Hello?
什么? 不 我不是… 稍等
What? No, I don't-- wait a minute.
所有位置都订满了
We're all booked up,
不过看起来十点钟有个空缺
but it looks like we have an opening at 10:00.
名字是 Bochner 两位
Bochner for two.
靠窗的座位? 别得寸进尺了
Window seat? Don't push it.
- Will… - 我正在吃晚餐
- Will-- - I am in the middle of dinner.
不 才不是 你已经在喝咖啡了
No, you're not. You're already on coffee.
好吧 我已经在喝咖… 你在哪?
Okay, so I'm on cof-- where are you?
这是秘密
It's a secret.
现在 告诉我 这感觉可不好受吧?
Now, tell me. How does that make you feel?
我感觉像是劣质血腥片里的联谊会女孩
Like a sorority girl in a bad slasher movie.
你在哪里?!
Where are you?!
这么说吧
Let's just put it this way,
"这通电话就是从这间屋子里打来的"
"the call is coming from inside the house."
1979年惊悚电影《来电惊魂》(When a Stranger Calls) 经典桥段
Grace 你现在不能呆在这
Grace, you cannot be here right now.
- 快回去 - 不
- Go home. - No.
- 回去! - 不
- Go home! - No.
- 走! - 不
- Go! - No.
不好意思
Excuse me.
请问你能把那个红发女疯子赶走吗?
Would you mind having that crazed redhead removed?
听我说 我是 Ricky Ricardo
Listen to me, I'm Ricky Ricardo.
美国经典情景喜剧 I Love Lucy 男主角
- 我会处理好的 Ricardo先生 - 不
- I'll take care of it, Mr. Ricardo. - No.
不好意思
Excuse me.
算了吧 这太不理智了 请让她进来吧
Look, this is insane. Let her in, please.
好的 发生了什么事? 你需要一个肺吗?
Okay, what is it? Do you need a lung?
我有两个 选一个 只要不再瞒东瞒西就好
I have two. Pick one. Just no more secrets.
- Grace 我什么都告诉你了 - K是谁?
- Grace, I tell you everything. - Who is K?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you.
Grace 你来这里做什么?
Grace, what are you doing here?
亲爱的 你怎么了? 你看起来像张没铺的床
Honey, what happened to you? You look like an unmade bed.
Karen 你不是去度假了吗
Karen, you're supposed to be on vacation.
Grace 向你介绍我的客户 K
Grace, I'd like you to meet my client, K.
- 嘿 - 嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
让我给你补充下我今天晚上都做了什么
Let me fill you in on the rest of my evening,
这样你就不会觉得我有事瞒着你
so you don't think I'm keeping anything from you.
Will
Will.
回家路上 我从小贩那买了一份椒盐卷饼
On the way home, I bought a pretzel from a vendor.
我觉得他的名字是 Luba 我刮掉了上面一半的盐
I think his name was Luba. And I scraped off half the salt.
- 别这样 - 然后我去了书店
- Come on. - Then I was in the bookstore
心不在焉地翻了翻
and I was absentmindedly thumbing through
美国女星 以超常记忆力闻名 七十年代出演剧集 Taxi
在垃圾桶里捡到的《Marilu Henner 的人生指南》
"Marilu Henner's Guide To Life." It was in the bargain bin.
你知道她从五岁开始就能劈叉了吗?
She has been able to do the split since she was five?
- 还有拇囊炎真是她的煎熬 - 我懂你的意思了
- And bunions are her personal hell. - I get the point.
然后 我快到家的时候
Then, when I was almost home,
我觉得我认出了街上的一个人
I thought I recognized someone on the street,
所以我抬手抬到一半想打招呼 却发现他不是我认识的那个人
so I sort of half-waved, but then it wasn't who I thought it was,
然后我就顺势假装挠了下耳朵… 只想让你知道
so I pretended to scratch my ear-- just so you know.
- 够了 见好就收! - 有什么大不了的 Grace?
- Enough, already! - What's the deal, Grace?
我没告诉你 Steven 的事又怎样 那只是场愚蠢的恋情
So I don't tell you about Steven. It was a stupid affair.
我并不为此感到自豪 我知道如果我告诉了你
I wasn't particularly proud of it, and I knew if I told you,
我就得真心地审视它
I'd have to really examine it,
但我只是真心想忘掉它
when I really wanted it to go away.
但 Will 如果我觉得你在隐瞒什么的话
But, Will, if I think you're hiding something,
我总是觉得你隐瞒的事情
I'm always gonna think that you're hiding something
比实际情况要严重得多
that's much bigger than it really is.
你为什么会这样想?
Why would you think that?
因为我不想再经历一遍你对我出柜的场景了
Because I don't want you to tell me that you're gay again.
什么?
What?
我们读大学的时候 那时圣诞节休假中
When we were in college, and at Christmas break
你对我出柜
you told me you were gay,
一切都不一样了
everything changed.
当然都不一样了 我整个人生都不一样了
Of course it changed. My whole life changed.
我的也是
So did mine.
所有事都解决了 但我总觉得我在隐隐等着
Everything worked out, but I guess I'm just still waiting
你的下一个…
for you to--
惊天大秘密来改变我的人生
change my world with your next big secret.
你差点就说了"颠覆我的世界" 对不对?
You almost said "Rock my world," Didn't you?
也许吧
Maybe.
Gracie...
出柜这种事 一生只用做一次的
coming out of the closet is something you only do once in life.
你要知道 就像出生一样
You know, it's like being born
或者是看"魔术师"约翰逊的脱口秀
or watching Magic Johnson's talk show.
美国著名篮球运动员 退役后开了一档脱口秀节目 The Magic Hour
我保证 不会再有惊心动魄的事情了
I promise, no more big surprises.
很好
Good.
还有一件事我需要向你坦白
There is one more I should tell you about.
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
本字幕仅供交流使用，版权归版权方所有，请勿用于商业用途，请于下载后24内小时内删除。
关注@WillGraceJackKaren蜜友帮 & 威尔和格蕾丝百度贴吧